One hundred two point two.
(Sheldon:)Exactly what it was half an hour ago.
(Sheldon:)It's like you're not even trying to get better.
(Amy:)Sheldon, you don't get over the flu
in half an hour.
(Sheldon:)Well, not with that attitude.
You know, I have to say,
I'm finding your bedside manner a little lacking.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry. I just want you to get better
as soon as possible.
(Sheldon:)And with that goal in mind,
let me ask you a question.
(Sheldon:)Do you believe in the placebo effect?
(Amy:)Of course I do. There have been many studies
proving its validity.
(Sheldon:)Great. Now, this may look like a Tic Tac...
(Sheldon:)...but it is really a powerful medication
specifically designed...
(Sheldon:)...to cure your illness,
as well as freshen your breath.
(Amy:)Sheldon, this isn't helping.